https://www.solutionsinplastic.com/privacy-policy/

Signature Plastics'Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for solutionsinplastic.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Orders
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we’ll use this information to contact you.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Surveys & Contests
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
Cookies
PMK uses cookies and similar technologies to help us provide, protect, and improve our services. Cookies enable you to use our site, remember your preferences, tell us which parts of our site you have visited, measure the effectiveness of our ad campaigns, and provide insights into our customers.
Functionality Cookies
These cookies help you navigate the website and use its features. For example, it may store your geographic location so we can provide you with a localized experience, enable shopping cart services, and help you access certain parts of the website.
Analytics and Performance Cookies
We use cookies to collect information to better understand how people use our website. For example, we use Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our website, browse or use our website, and highlight areas where we can improve (such as navigation, shopping experience, and marketing campaigns).
Advertising Cookies
Our partners use cookies and pixels to help us deliver ads, make ads more relevant to you, and to track ad campaign performance. For example, Facebook cookies determine whether we’ve shown an ad and provide us with information about how you interacted with the ad.
We may also allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and in applications, and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, device identifiers, and other technologies to collect information about your use of our websites and mobile applications, and other websites and applications, such as your IP address, web browser information, mobile network information, pages viewed, time spent on pages or in apps, links clicked, and conversion information. This information may be used by PMK and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests, and better understand your online and in-app activity.
Your Choices
You can opt-out of seeing interest-based ads from participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page, the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page, or http://youronlinechoices.eu. Your mobile device may also include a feature that allows you to opt out of having certain information collected through apps used for behavioral advertising purposes. Please note that turning off advertising cookies will not mean that you are not served any advertising, but rather that it will not be tailored to you.
To opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising or customize Google display network ads, you can visit the Google Ads Settings page. You can prevent Google from collecting and processing data generated by the cookie and your use of our website, as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the Google browser plug-in. Your browser or device may offer settings that allow you to choose whether cookies are set and to delete them. Visit your browser or device “Settings” or “Help” menus for more details.
Because some cookies are a part of the functionality of the website, disabling them may prevent you from using certain parts of the website.
Changes to Our Cookie Policy
We may change this Cookie Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy, and in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review the Cookie Policy frequently to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 360.366.5044 or sales@solutionsinplastic.com.
CONTACT USfor a free quote
We'll develop your custom keycaps from start to finish
Name*
First
Name
Last
PhoneEmail*
UntitledCAPTCHACommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
